♪♪
No.
Absolutely not.
I'm telling you, we
need more time.
You've got a lot of nerve
coming to us with this now.
Ed, you've got to handle this.
How? How?!
What the hell am
I supposed to do?
Tim. Tim?
Would you tell me
what's going on?
What do you mean?
I feel like I'm in the
middle of a psychodrama,
and I don't know
what it's all about.
You're imagining things.
Don't treat me
like I don't belong!
I'm as much a part of
this company as you are.
Jerry, relax!
I don't want to relax!
Someone's got to tell me
what's going on in this place.
Hi, Jeff.
Hi. We're having lunch today.
Ed's in there with him.
Why don't you have a seat?
Oh. Jeff.
Come in.
Maybe we should,
uh, reschedule lunch?
Would you mind?
Of course not.
Are you okay?
No.
Well, you want to talk about it?
It might make you feel better.
You know something?
You're right.
Remember Ed Billings, the
president of the company?
Sure.
He just fired me.
- You?
- Yeah. Me.
Welcome to the
world of business.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
We're going to lunch.
Remember two summers ago
when you worked in my lab?
I'd just started a
research project.
- Yeah, on... on hair growth.
- That's right.
Well, it turned out better
than anyone thought.
It worked?
Big-time.
Billings & Massler's
gonna make millions
when the product comes out.
So why did
Mr. Billings fire you?
So they don't have to
split the profits with me.
They can't fire you like
that just out of the blue.
You know, I was such an idiot.
Ed's been jumping down my throat
the past couple of months.
I thought he was having
personal problems.
He was setting me up,
getting ready to dump me.
So can't you just take the
formula someplace else?
The company owns it, Jeff.
They own everything I create.
If I try to sell it
somewhere else,
Ed'll claim I stole it and sue.
Besides, I don't even
have my notes and samples.
They're in my lab.
Ed's posting a security
guard at the door
to make sure I don't go in.
I can't believe this!
You?
Man, I was looking at millions.
You know... I could get in.
What do you mean?
Well, I know
where everything is.
I-I know the lab.
I could sneak in.
I could get your notes
and those samples.
Forget it.
All I need is your
security pass.
I could do it tonight.
You could get caught.
I worked there for three months.
I know the place like
the back of my hand.
Fine.
Here.
My security card.
The key to the
refrigerator lock. Oh...
The combination to the safe.
You sure you'll be all right?
It's no problem.
♪♪
Hey! Hold it!
Hey!
Hey! Stop!
The good news is,
I got the notebook.
The bad news is, is
that I lost the samples.
I tripped and fell, and
they all broke. I'm sorry.
That's all right.
My notes are all I really need.
You did it.
There's one other thing.
You know Harry,
the security guard?
Yeah.
I think he recognized me.
What? What?!
Uh, yeah... Hello?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I
remember Jeff Duvall.
He painted my house one time.
What are you calling me in
the middle of the night for?!
You did what?!
N... No!
No, I'm not coming
down to that jail at...
3:00 in the morning!
No, you get on a cot
somewhere and go to sleep,
and I'll see you tomorrow!
Good...
I didn't think I'd get caught,
and-and I wouldn't have if it
wouldn't have been
for that damn guard.
I mean, I still can't believe
he remembered me.
I only worked
there three months!
I should have worn a mask.
Jeff, it's not that you got
caught; you committed a crime.
Well, so did Billings & Massler
when they fired Dr. Crider.
No.
What, you're gonna tell
me that you don't think
what they did to him was wrong?
- The law...
- I wasn't stealing anything.
I was helping a friend get back
something that
was stolen from him.
And if they want to
throw me in prison for that,
well, then that's just fine.
You used to be a pretty
good housepainter,
but your mind's
really screwed up.
What happened to you?
Thanks a lot.
Well, I'm sorry.
At 3:00 in the morning,
I can't pull my punches.
- Hey, where are you going?
- Home.
You just can't leave
me here like this.
What's one night in jail
for somebody that thinks
going to prison's swell? Guard!
- I don't want to go to prison!
- Don't do that!
Don't shake me!
Uh... uh...
- I-I'm sorry.
- A-All these people want's
their notebook back.
If they get that back, maybe
they'll drop the charges.
I gave it to Dr. Crider.
Okay. Guard!
- They really are his notes.
- Okay. Guard?
3:00 in the morning.
Yeah. Yeah.
Mr. Cr... Mr. Crider?
- Yes? - Oh... Hi. Hi.
I'm, uh, I'm Ben
Matlock, a-a lawyer.
Whew! Excuse me, I...
I was up half the night.
I-I represent Jeff Duvall.
He was arrested last
night for that burglary.
What burglary?
Out at the lab.
They had a burglary last night?
Yeah. Jeff broke in
and stole your notes
for your baldness cure.
Why on earth would
he steal my notes?
I thought you told him to.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Excuse me.
Well, I don't intend to tell
anybody at your company
that you're involved, if
that's what you're afraid of.
All I want is for you
to give me the notes,
so I can give 'em back to them,
and then we can forget this
whole thing ever happened.
My notes are under
lock and key at the lab.
At least, they'd better be.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, I've got to get to work.
Work? I thought
you'd been fired.
Who the hell told you that?
Jeff.
I like Jeff.
He's a very hard worker,
and someday, I expect he'll
make an excellent chemist.
But he is a little flaky.
Now, excuse me.
He gave me the pass card,
the, the key to the
refrigerator lock,
the combination to the
safe, and he denied it?
He denied everything.
Why?
I don't know.
If Billings & Massler don't
get that notebook back,
I'm in real trouble.
That's right.
I can't believe it; I was
trying to do him a favor.
Jeff, what you did
was really dumb.
It was so dumb, I believe you.
I'll get you out on bail.
Then what?
I don't know.
Housepainters are hard to find.
You still know how
to handle a brush?
So, what do you think, Tim?
How far behind does this put us?
Four months, maybe six.
Even with the
samples we still have?
If we didn't have those samples,
we'd be behind a full year.
What do you want
me to tell the press?
The truth... that the
formula for the hair restorer
that we were on the verge
of marketing was stolen,
but we are actively
engaged in redeveloping it
and hope to be in
production within six months.
Shall I use the name Folliderm?
Why not?
That is the name
we're marketing it under.
Nothing wrong with
giving it a little exposure.
You're still working.
You told me you had been fired.
You lied to me, Tim.
What the hell's going on?
- Somebody get security.
- Who is this guy?
The kid who broke
- in here last night.
- It was all a setup.
You used me to
steal your own formula
so that you could peddle
it to the highest bidder
and I could take the heat.
- That's ridiculous.
- Do yourself some good, Jeff.
I suggest you get out of here.
He told me that
he had been fired.
He told me that you
guys were ripping him off.
He told me to steal his notes
so that we could take his
discovery to another company.
It was all his idea.
I was just his patsy.
- Get him out of here.
- Right away, sir.
How do you think that
I got in here last night?
How do you think that I knew
the combination to the safe?
He gave it to me, that's how.
He gave me his security
card and his keys.
Get him
- out of here!
- Come on, let's go.
What kind of creep are you?
How could you do this to me?
Come on, let's go.
Tim.
Tim?
Ah, he's supposed to be bowling,
but his car's
still in the drive.
Tim?
Wait... Hello.
Oh.
Oh, Jeff, what did
you break into tonight?
What?!
Somebody planted the
murder weapon in my truck.
There was no knife there
when I parked for the night.
I'm telling you,
someone planted it there.
I-I went over to
the lab yesterday.
Tim Crider was there.
He lied to me about being fired.
I mean, I was
completely flipped out.
He-He made me
feel sorry for him,
and he, and he got me to
do all his dirty work for him.
And I wanted to see if he had
the nerve to deny it to my face,
and he did.
Couple of guards
came and threw me out.
I mean, they were all there...
Ed Billings, uh, Dr. Massler,
and some other
guy that I don't know.
Who's Dr. Massler?
The head chemist,
cofounder of the company.
What?
Sit down.
Now...
tomorrow we're
going to court again,
and your parents are going
to come up with bail again.
And then you're going
to go home again,
but one thing's gonna change.
You're not going to call
me to come down here
in the middle of
the night again.
- I understand.
- All right.
You're gonna go
home, hit the books,
help your mama wash the dishes,
clean your paintbrushes,
stay out of trouble.
You got that?
Guard!
Go home... stay out of trouble.
Well... Good morning, Bob.
Oh, morning, Ben.
Ah, don't tell me the
Duvall kid is your client.
He painted my house one time.
Have you found anything?
My, aren't we testy here?
I didn't get much
sleep last night, so...
Okay.
Well, uh, we're pretty sure
that the murder weapon came
from Dr. Crider's,
uh, tool kit here.
His wife remembers
seeing him using it
in here a couple mornings ago.
Uh-huh.
Where was his wife that night?
She was at the mall
with a couple of friends.
Seems, uh, he went bowling
every Wednesday night.
She went shopping.
Now, her friends remember
that, uh, Tim Crider was
alive when they picked her up
and, uh, he was dead by
the time they dropped her off.
I promise it's
gonna be all right.
Is that Mrs. Crider?
Yeah.
Uh, the word is that, uh...
her husband found
a cure for baldness.
What's that?
That's the cure.
Uh, "Folliderm,"
I think they call it.
Why don't you try it?
What?
What do you got to lose?
Give it a try.
Come on, Ben.
They never have found a cure
for baldness, and they never will.
What do you take
me for... A chump?
Yeah, but... what if this is it?
Aren't you curious?
I am.
Give it a try.
You grow a little bit of
hair, I'll give you 50 bucks.
Forget it.
Well, I-I-I'd just
feel stupid doing it.
Just forget it.
Forget it.
What the hell?
Try and get some sleep.
Uh, Mrs. Crider,
uh, I'm Ben Matlock.
I represent Jeff Duvall.
I'm sorry, but I would just
as soon not talk to you.
Okay.
Your husband, uh... your
husband was a bowler.
Every Wednesday night.
I bet he was good.
Uh, Mrs. Crider,
I'm looking for a black
loose-leaf notebook
about yea thick.
Would you have seen it
anywhere around the house?
Tim was looking through
a notebook like that
yesterday morning.
He put it down right over here.
It's gone.
Uh, would you mind waiting?
And I'll tell
Mr. Billings you're here.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, and your name again is...?
Ben Matlock.
Thank you.
- Yes?
- Oh, excuse me, Mr. Billings.
There's a Mr. Matlock
outside who wants to see you.
- Matlock?
- Mr. Ben Matlock.
Did you tell him I was in?
Yes, I did, sir.
All right, tell him
that I'll be right out.
Very well.
Excuse me.
He'll be right with you.
Thank you.
Mr. Matlock?
Oh, yeah.
- I'm Ed Billings.
- Ah.
Yes, I'm sorry,
I didn't get the message
that you were dropping by.
I didn't leave one.
If it's inconvenient,
I can come back.
No, no, is there
anything I can do for you?
Sit down.
Well, uh, the paper said
that the theft of your formula
could set you back,
uh, almost three months.
Oh, that was when
Tim Crider was alive.
Now that he's gone, I don't
know what's going to happen.
Oh.
What do you think it
would have cost you
if Dr. Crider sold the
formula to the competition?
Tim would have
no reason to do that.
He had a lucrative contract;
he stood to make millions.
Well, he told my client
that you didn't want to
share the profits with him.
I'm afraid that your
client is lying to you.
Why don't you drop by the
office and look at Tim's contract?
Now, is there anything else?
Yeah, yeah, I-I-I want to know
who was with you and Dr. Massler
when my client
confronted Dr. Crider.
Why do you ask?
Uh, well... well,
I believe that book was
more valuable than a jewel.
I am told that in time, your
formula might have been worth
hundreds of millions of dollars.
And one of you might
have believed what Jeff said.
And one of you might have
gone to Dr. Crider's that night
in an attempt to
get that book back,
and when that attempt
failed, you framed my client.
That's a ridiculous idea, sir.
Who else was in the room?
Jerry Hughes, our PR man.
Ah.
Just out of curiosity, uh,
where were you that night?
At my office working until
8:15, and then I drove home.
Okay, okay.
So what time do you want
me to stop by your office?
For what?
To look at
Dr. Crider's contract.
How does 3:00 sound?
Perfect, perfect, 3:00.
Fortunately, not all
the Folliderm samples were lost,
so we're breaking
down those that are left
and analyzing the components.
Ah, sort of working backwards.
Mm-hmm, I hope
we can do it in time.
In time for what?
Oh, in time to get the product
out before anyone else does.
And the future of your
company depends on it...
Your future, too.
What do you mean?
You and Ed Billings put
up a million dollars apiece
to get your company going.
You had to mortgage everything
you and your family had.
And three years later,
the company paid me back.
But then, last year, the company
needed another infusion of cash,
so you and Ed Billings
put up $3 million apiece.
You mortgaged
yourself to the hilt,
and you did it because
Tim Crider was going to have
a marketable product in, hmm,
12 to 18 months, and you knew
you'd never have to
worry about money again.
Didn't you feel betrayed when
Jeff said he stole the formula
so Dr. Crider could
sell it to someone else?
I didn't believe
that for a second.
Well, then you
won't mind my asking
where you were Wednesday night.
My alibi?
I was here in the
lab working... alone.
Mmm.
You know, if Dr. Crider
didn't help Jeff break in here,
who did?
I mean, where'd
he get a pass card,
and the key to the refrigerator,
and the combination to the safe?
Somebody had to help him.
All I know is it
doesn't make sense
for Tim to have
stolen his own formula.
Maybe your client figured
out a way to bypass security
when he used to work here.
You knew, uh... you
knew Dr. Crider well?
We bowled together
every Wednesday night.
Oh, that's right. I
saw your picture
- with the team at his house.
- Oh.
Did he get along with the
people he worked with?
Yes.
I wonder if...
I wonder if he
stole that formula
not to make himself richer,
but to make
somebody else poorer.
You mean to get
back at somebody?
Well, the way I understand it,
everybody in the company
stood to profit off his discovery.
Well, all of us who own stock
would have, that's for sure.
Our president, Ed
Billings, was trying to time it
so that the company
would go public
just as Folliderm was released,
pretty much
guaranteeing that the stock
- would go through the roof.
- Through the roof. Yeah.
So, a lot of people
besides Dr. Crider
would've become
millionaires, huh?
What's more important,
- I would've gotten my hair back.
- Oh.
Yeah.
Yes?
All right, I'll tell him.
That was Ed.
He has a copy of Tim's
contract ready and waiting.
Oh, good. Good.
Uh, nice to talk to you.
Oh.
How you doing, sir?
Here you are.
♪♪
It's that way.
So, I went back to the bar,
and I snuck a peek at his tab.
- Yeah.
- His name's Julian Ingersol.
- Mm-hmm.
- He's in room 1627.
- Yeah.
- Registered there
the day before
Dr. Crider was murdered.
Yeah.
What'd the fellow look like?
Big guy. Big guy.
Broad shoulders
like a linebacker,
blond hair pulled
back in a ponytail.
That sounds like a guy
I saw slipping out of the
back door of Ed Billings' house.
Sneaking around a lot, huh?
Yeah. Wh-What
was in that briefcase?
Payoffs.
Who knows?
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
Tim Crider had a
good... good contract.
He lied to Jeff about
getting ripped off,
just like he lied to
him about getting fired.
Now, daggone!
Who'd give me that?
You're supposed to get something
for Christmas you can use,
or at least eat.
It was you.
Next year, fruitcake.
I love fruitcake.
I bought that for you
so I could borrow it.
You can't borrow fruitcake.
Look at that.
What are you doing here?
I was just... I was
just getting your tray.
I knocked, but you must
not have heard me, sir.
Knock more loudly next time, ja?
You bet. You bet.
Be happy to. My mistake.
So, Bob Brooks had the
lab lift a couple of prints
off the stuff from the tray.
Ran 'em through the computer.
- Hmm.
- Came up dry.
No criminal record, huh?
Yeah, the man talks with
a heavy European accent.
I think he's German
or Swiss or something.
So, Bob sent the
prints over to Interpol.
Maybe they can come
up with something there.
That'd take a long time.
Yeah.
Hey.
Finally getting the
hang of this thing, huh?
I read the directions.
Yeah.
D-Did you get a look
at this guy's phone bill?
He only talked to one
person since he's been here.
Ed Billings.
Never at his office.
Always at home.
And I also found out
who picked up
Mr. Ingersol's tab.
Not Ed Billings?
Nope.
Well, who is it, then?
Sure.
Okay.
Dr. Massler?
Yes?
Who's Julian Ingersol?
The man who's staying
at the Fairview Hotel.
Well, all his expenses are
being charged to your credit card.
See?
Here's a copy of the
imprint that was made
when he registered.
This has nothing to
do with your client.
Well, maybe it does,
maybe it doesn't.
What about Dr. Crider's murder?
It has nothing to
do with that, either.
You and Ed Billings
had fights with Tim Crider.
They were
discussions, not fights.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, I'm very busy.
I think that's why Tim
Crider stole that formula.
He was angry.
So angry he decided
to make sure neither one of you
made a dime from his discovery.
Wrong on all counts, Ms. Thomas.
Now, I'm sorry, but
I have work to do.
I've got the pH level on that,
uh, on that slide
that you wanted...
Oh, very good. Thanks...
♪♪
I don't care what he knows
or how he found out about it.
It just doesn't matter.
We're not going to let
some meddlesome lawyer
keep us from doing...
Keep you from doing what?
What the hell is this?
Have you been following me?
Well, sure.
I was following you,
and he was following him,
and she was following her.
Oh, Dr. Crider's notebook.
So, tell me,
did one of you kill him,
or were all of you in on it?
None of us killed him.
Yeah.
You see this?
It's worthless.
The formula's worthless.
Folliderm doesn't work.
Tim Crider knew it.
Dr. Massler and I knew it.
There was no reason for any
of us to kill for this notebook.
What the devil's going on?
About six months ago, we decided
to test Folliderm with people.
Well, it was a miracle.
Within three weeks,
people who had no hair
began growing hair.
People who had hair
began growing more hair.
But then...
about two months
ago, all of a sudden,
the new hair fell out.
Like that, it was gone.
What if you continued
using the drug?
Didn't work.
When the new hair fell out,
there was no new growth.
Folliderm was a bust.
Well, why... why
steal the notebook?
To buy time.
In the early part
of the testing,
we decided to take
the company public.
With a cure for baldness,
the stock'd go through the roof.
The stock... It was Tim's idea.
We needed time to
make the drug work.
But you set up Jeff.
We were between a
rock and a hard place.
If we delayed the offering,
people would think
something was wrong.
If we had the
offering and no drug,
we'd never get our price.
We set up this lab
so Tim could continue
his research in secret.
We brought Dr. Ingersol
over from Europe to help.
Everyone at the lab's
in a mad scramble
to rediscover Tim's formula.
No one knows anything
about this place or that the real
name of the game is
fixing Tim's formula.
Oh...
Why are you doing that?
Huh?
Smiling like that.
Oh, I don't know.
I just think I might
know someone
who thought that notebook
was worth killing for.
I really appreciate your
meeting me here like this.
I had to pick up a
few things, anyway.
I've been staying with friends.
If you don't mind, I'd
like to get this over with.
Uh, what is it you
wanted to ask me?
Okay, uh, what time
did you leave the house
to go shopping that night?
7:30.
And what time did your husband
usually leave the
house to go bowling?
He had to be there at 8:00,
so he usually left
about quarter till.
Mm-hmm.
Did, uh, did everyone on
the team have a jacket?
You had to have two
things to be on the team:
an average of at
least 130 and a jacket.
How tall was your
husband? About 6' 2"?
Exactly 6' 2".
Yeah...
So, you've been
head of public relations
at Billings & Massler for
how long, Mr. Hughes?
Seven years.
Are you good at it?
Well, I think so, yes.
Well, how come you've never
gotten a raise or even a bonus?
Well, I have. Every
year, I've gotten both.
Except instead of
giving it to you in cash,
they give it to you in
shares of company stock.
So, uh, how many shares
would you say that you own now?
Around 5,000, I guess.
Yeah.
So, if everything
has gone as planned,
and Billings & Massler
had been able to market
Dr. Crider's hair restorer
about the same time
the company went public,
why, you stood to make, what?
Hundreds of thousands of dollars
on your shares? Maybe millions?
- I guess.
- Boy.
So, seven years of,
uh, deferred gratification
and blind faith would
have finally paid off.
Is that right?
I don't know what you mean.
You must've been very devastated
when Dr. Crider's formula
was stolen from that lab.
And you must've been very angry
when my client burst in
there the next morning
and revealed the person
responsible for that theft
was none other than
Dr. Crider himself.
There was no reason
for Dr. Crider to
steal his own formula.
He stood to gain
more than I did.
Y-Y-You didn't think
maybe, j-just maybe,
that he didn't do it for
financial gain, but he did it
to get back at the
company for something?
No.
You didn't think maybe,
just maybe, it had
something to do with those
long closed-door arguments
he had with the
company president?
- No.
- You had no doubts whatsoever?
I said "no."
Then why did you go
to his house the
night of the murder?
I didn't.
Yes, you did,
and I can prove it.
Mrs. Crider is
prepared to testify that,
three days ago, I
removed this jacket
from the room in which
her husband was murdered.
Do you recognize it?
It's a jacket from the
company bowling team.
You have one just
like it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Oh, what size do you wear?
- Small.
- Can you be more specific?
What size is the jacket
you're wearing now?
Thirty-six.
So, whose jacket
you think this is?
Well... must be Tim's.
It's yours.
And I know for two reasons.
One, Tim Crider wore a size 44.
This is a size 36.
And two, I compared this jacket
with all the other
jackets on the team.
This one has a different zipper.
You had to have the zipper
on your jacket
replaced, didn't you?
Didn't you?
Yes.
So, this is your
jacket, isn't it?
My jacket was at his
house, because we had
mixed them up at the
bowling alley the week before.
He grabbed mine. I grabbed his.
And neither of us realized it
- until we got home.
- Oh.
We were going to
switch them back
at the alley that night.
Only he never showed up.
Yeah. I see, I see.
Well, the night of the murder,
did you go straight from your
house to the bowling alley?
I already said
that's what I did.
I think you're
forgetting something.
That's right. I-I... I
picked up a prescription
for my wife at the drugstore.
Yeah, yeah. What
were you wearing?
I don't remember.
I think you know, uh,
Mr. Jack Greenstein.
The gentleman
from the drugstore.
He waited on you that
night, and he remembers.
And he's prepared to
testify that you were wearing
a black bowling jacket.
Now, since you say
that you and Tim Crider
had switched jackets,
you must've been
wearing his jacket.
Is that correct?
Yeah, as I say...
Tim Crider wore a size 44.
This is a size 44.
Would you mind standing up
and putting it on?
Please do as you're asked.
Yeah.
There you go...
Yeah, there you are.
There you go.
Look at that. Look at that.
Talk about a bad fit.
Your hands don't even
come out the sleeves.
Mr. Greenstein told me
that the night of the murder,
you were wearing a
jacket that fit you perfectly.
Certainly, he would
have remembered...
Anybody would have
remembered... If he'd seen you
wearing a jacket that
fit as badly as this one
or looked as awful as
this one does on you.
Please sit down.
You were wearing your jacket
the night of the murder, and you
left it at Tim Crider's house
after you killed
him, didn't you?
You knew that what
my client had said
about Tim Crider
stealing his own formula
might very well be true.
You knew something was
going on down at that lab.
And you believed
in that formula.
You believed that notebook
could make you a millionaire.
So, you went over
to Tim Crider's house
to talk to him.
He opened the
door. He let you in.
You took off your
jacket. You sat down.
You talked.
But you didn't hear
what you wanted to hear.
And you got mad... furious.
And you reached in his toolbox
and you got his knife,
and you stabbed him with it.
And then you
realized he was dead.
Then you realized my client
was perfectly positioned
to take the fall for you.
But in your haste to leave
and plant the murder
weapon in my client's truck
and get over to the
bowling alley for your alibi...
you picked up the wrong jacket.
Didn't you, Mr. Hughes?
We find the
defendant not guilty.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
This court is adjourned.
Bob, what you doing here?
Well, I got a little
surprise for you, Ben.
You told me you'd
give me 50 bucks
if that Folliderm
stuff really worked.
Hmm?
I don't believe it.
What do you think?
I don't know, Bob.
It's-It's not you.
I mean, you've got hair,
but something's missing.
He's right.
Something is missing.
You know what's missing?
Hmm?
That virility you had
when you were bald.
You know, like Yul
Brynner, Telly Savalas,
even Daddy Warbucks.
It's that take-charge,
two-fisted, he-man, macho look.
Sexy.
Sexy?
Definitely.
Forget the 50.
www.tvsubtitles.net